[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1997 movie Devils Advocate, Keanu Reeves character, Kevin Lomax, starts work in John Miltons huge law firm. Which one of these actors played Milton?", "correct_answer": "Al Pacino", "incorrect_answers": ["Jeffrey Jones", "Val Kilmer", "Robert De Niro"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Between the 1980s and 2006 Borneo lost approximately 45 % of its rain forests due to logging.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the name of the Koh-i-Noor diamond mean in Persian?", "correct_answer": "Mountain of light", "incorrect_answers": ["Eye of the sea", "Divine treasure", "Soul of a virgin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Planes, Trains  Automobiles, where did Neal Page and Del Griffiths plane land instead of their final destination?", "correct_answer": "Wichita, KS", "incorrect_answers": ["Kansas City, MO", "Topeka, KS", "Tulsa, OK"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Before Johnny Depp did it in Fear and Loathing in Las Vegas, which famous actor portrayed a character based on Hunter Thompson in the movie Where the Buffalos roam?", "correct_answer": "Bill Murray", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim Carrey", "David Caradine", "Chevy Chase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did an airplane first hit 200 miles per hour?", "correct_answer": "1922", "incorrect_answers": ["1944", "1955", "1933"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This snake, the only existing member of its family, can be found in Mexico and has a very muscular body and a shovel-shaped snout.", "correct_answer": "Loxocemidae bicolor", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Dwarf boa", "Pipe snake"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "After his fight with Apollo Creed in Rocky IV, what was Ivan Drago re-nicknamed?", "correct_answer": "Death From Above", "incorrect_answers": ["Death From Below", "Death From Communism", "Death From Russia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This tiny Caribbean island is shared by France and the Netherlands.", "correct_answer": "St. Martin", "incorrect_answers": ["St. Lucia", "St. Mark", "St. Bartholomew"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed the first Bond movie, Doctor No, in 1962?", "correct_answer": "Terence Young", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter R. Hunt", "Guy Hamilton", "John Glen"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Urine and semen are expelled in the urethra.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A ionic compound with H (hydrogen) in the front is most likely to be which of the following?", "correct_answer": "acid", "incorrect_answers": ["base", "water", "indicator"]}]